And and some referral team announcements. I think you guys are gonna be pretty excited about. I can't give you all the details. We're gonna give you some of those details, right? So anyways, and Cole, you're always smiling. I love it. You're like the happiest guy. No, I love it, man.
Life is good.
You're just crushing it, by the way. Thanks, Cole, for all the hard work you're doing on proposal calls and everything else you're doing. It's really… it's really coming around. So all right. So let me give some updates before I get into EHP. And again, if you're new to either one of my companies, I want to welcome you. This is the place that business professionals go to do the work once and get paid for 5, 10, 20 years.
So you can own your life, and so you're only going to be able to do that by bringing massive benefits into companies. And we've got some new stuff coming out I want to share with you. Um, so we're really going to stay focused on about 4. You know, I told you 2026 is going to be quite an epic year for all of you.
Um, that are working. So, um, a couple items. So, um… I first want to talk about Legacy One partners, those people that are, you know, doing legal show as benefits into companies. We're going to be having a big New Orleans event that's coming up the 9th through 12th. I hope you've signed up. I can't wait to see my wife and I are coming out, and a lot of our leadership is, too. That's great. We have a small business training.
for certifications for anyone that wants to get paid on the voluntary benefits going into companies, right? They already have 43,000 companies that offer this, and that's the 18th level 1 and 2 is all. It's our last one. They're going to combine.
They did it just for us because we're special. We're always special, right? They always said, we're always special. So it's our last thing. And then on the 24th, we have a small business training. So I can't wait to see everyone out in New Orleans. I can't wait to see that. That's that that's kind of our company event. So make sure you're set up in that.
Number two, I want to just to reinforce last week y'all had a call with 24-7 Consultancy, you know, previously. That's always been the company. They had PSP in front of it, so now it's 24-7 consultants. It's always been that way, which is great, because now they can see the history.
the credibility that that company has. 10 years, by the way, over 2,000 clients and 100% retention. I want to repeat that 100% retention. So if you know a doctor, a dentist, I hope you all have a dentist, right? I know Cole's got one, because he's got… he's always smiling, he's got great teeth.
So he's got a dentist. But if you got a dentist, a chiropractor, a doctor, you have a hospital, surgical center, you want to make a fortune, you want to have a great service. I'm telling you, 24/7 consultants going to be epic. Next week, they're going to be on deck every other week. It's that important for your pocketbook.
Um, here's why they're successful, because they go in and they get 90% of accounts receivables, 98%. That's a bottom line of people's P. And L like never before. But they do that without changing the billers. They do that without a contract.
And they do that, they give a $5,000 audit away for free up front to the client, and their closing rates are epic. And so if you want to make big money, we have if you get to get a billion dollars combined in billing, whether that's from a big hospital.
or a bunch of small clinics or, you know, large conglomerates. That's a six figure monthly income. I want to repeat that. That's a six-figure monthly income, and they have 100%.
Right. Did they keep of course, who's going to move off of 98% accounts receivables? Of course they're going to stay on this. So, like, you guys not just need to run. You need to, like, marathon it and get those discovery calls. Do not sell the service, sell a discovery call.
sell that $5,000 free audit. Sell the fact that what's 98% on their P&L going to look like? They're gonna look… that CFO is going to look like a hero, right? They should be getting a raise. So get in people's face and getting directed and say, what planner are you from that you're not racing right now to get a.
You know, to get a discovery call, Mr. Or Mrs. Cfo, because here's what we're doing to your bottom line and your P&L. And and it's an awesome pitch. They're not changing anything, they're not having to sign contracts, they're not… I mean, it's it's… and that's the biggest thing that affects those companies, um.
Is that is that accounts receivables number? So get that done. We're going to be on deck next week. We're excited about that opportunity. We got some big stuff planned for that. Um, so I wanted to let you all know about that. And then, um… And then before… and then I'm gonna get into it. We have another service we're gonna be launching, and I've been working on this one for a while. It's contract engineering. I have shipping partners I've had for years. See, I'm a fan of of getting people out of the chaos of trading hours for dollars. To me, that's called prison, right? So if you get a corporate job, it's your… you can't will it, own it, sell it, or control it.
Someone's controlling you, and that means you're controlling your family, that means you're controlling your income. It's a fallacy to think that you're just going to stick with a job for 40 years, and your 401k is going to take care of you in life. It doesn't work that way, because life happens and affects that money. I want you to be able to control that yourself.
That's what we're so good at doing. We've been doing this for 25 years. That's our history. 25 years, tens of thousands of clients we've helped do billions of dollars in savings. We know this craft better than anyone in the country, right? So we're about bringing massive value to companies that can pay you, but they're going to stick like super glue.
Well, one of the vendors that I've had for years is a company called ShipStore. Well, it can take a while. Sometimes you, like me, I'm going to get gray hair waiting for you. I get it, but when you get it, their client's average stay in 20 years. So when's the last time you've been paid on 20 years on every shipping label? So ship store is great.
We're gonna put another product in front of it. You're going to have four shipping programs in one pitch, four programs in one pitch going to blow your mind. We're going to bring contract engineering. What's that? That's expense reduction. That's where you go in and we recover dollars that they're overpaying their shipping.
We redo their contracts, it's massive money, pays you within 90 days. And I'm going to show you guys how to make 20, 30, 40 grand with… with maybe 5 clients.
And it's awesome. And then back ending will be two other shipping products and ShipStore. So we're going to have an awesome entrance, fast money, big money, and those are three agreements that auto renew. And 70% of their clients auto renew.
So, it's gonna be a pretty awesome deal. Their average comp for you is gonna be probably about a $300,000 deal on the contract term. It's gonna be big. So, that's coming out.
Soon, I got my staff on the call, so I'm not going to give specific numbers, because then they shoot me after this call, and so I don't want to do that, but it's going to be coming out soon, but we're working on it right now. So that's going to be an awesome lane. Fast money, long-term money, and that's going to lead to all the other things that will pay you in perpetuity. That's how you pay.
your kids, right? Pastor Jim. That's how you really have accelerated income. So we're really super excited about that product. Finally, I want to talk about, and we're going to add some recruiting stuff in there for, um, for, um… For EHP, so I want to get into EHP here. So we do have an AI call tomorrow, by the way, everyone, so you know that you've got AI. But look, EHP's really been like a rocket ship. We started this journey last last summer.
Yeah.
And we put up numbers like no one's ever seen in the country. And but we also found out that we learned what works, what doesn't, what don't fit square pegs and around holes, right, Cole? What makes sense? What's going to go through? And we've closed a lot of business now, and I want to congratulate all of you that that done that. And I forgot to even give on a stock technology partner some love today, because.
We just closed some huge deals with Unframed. Jeff Matude, if you're out there, you are a stud. And lots of great stuff going on with that. Big accounts being closed that remember on a stock leads to multiple deals on tech. Every company in the country and the world qualifies for it.
So it's an epic service, but we're on the forefront of AI. You don't want to be the one explaining to your grandkids that, like, well, I had this AI thing, and I just kind of watched it come and go, right? That you don't want to have that story. You want to be part of the profitable story on that, right? And so that's exactly what they're doing. We have 5 different AI companies.
that on a stock is doing and presenting up front. That's on top of all the other technology stuff. There's some big data centers with some really big opportunities going on. So I just want to congratulate all of you that are that are working that. And we're now wanting to put, you know, we're putting some other stuff in front of you.
that can lead into quicker dollars while you're still doing that work. So but I wanted to. I wanted to congratulate all of you. But coming back to EHP, we're gonna… there's gonna be some big announcements, and I told you on this call and this text today that we, you know, start to tell you a little bit about. So.
Um, this product is really kind of the perfect culmination of timing right now in the US, especially in January, after all the, you know, the biggest healthcare increases ever have happened. Cole's talked about it, Marty's talked about it, 18% plus or better in healthcare increases.
But more importantly, what's their employees experience with some of the most record breaking employees are getting these massive deductibles like Cole, I don't even know how they afford it, to be honest. Like a family that's out of seven, eight, $9,000 deductible. What are they going to do?
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Yeah.
Like, because that's paycheck to paycheck folks out there, which we can't forget, that's most of the country, right? So so EHP really solves that. Many of you got smart. You adjusted your whole conversation in 2026 to just a healthcare pitch and not a tax pitch. You were smart to do that.
Because it's paying off. Now, what's also smart to get out of the rose-colored glasses to think you're going to do a 10, 20,000 employee company that does not… that's not the wheelhouse right now for this industry. There's about 7, 8 other companies. This one has pays the most, has the most robust program.
I'm definitely more comfortable with the legality side of how they're situated. But this thing is taking off across the Us. And so people are experiencing it now. And Cole's seen it firsthand because he's on proposal calls with EHP and he's closing up these clients. And he could tell you firsthand what's going on.
So first off, great for hanging in there. Some people in business throw up a couple clients and it doesn't go their way, and they give up. I think, you know, I think that's a tragedy. I think your dreams are much more worth than a couple misses. I think your family is worth more than a couple misses. I think your financial future is worth more than a couple misses, or not a perfect business.
And I think you need to see the forest through the trees, because those are people that make the money in life, right? There's no such thing. So there are some challenges with EHP that we have, but there's also some great aspects of EHP. But it's really starting to turn on because HP's adding a lot of stuff. It's really great.
Even though they're a fairly new company, they're very well heavily capitalized. And so, but there's some things that are going to run it. They're going to run into. So here's the good news.
There's… there's… I'm always telling you the two paths to riches in life are residuals and leveraging, and, you know, I wrote a book about it. We own that on a much larger scale, because when you can leverage a vendor like like EHP, for example, and how it pays, or you can leverage.
A large on a stock deal, you can leverage, you know, a 24 7 hospital, because you can't go in the country and go find a business that's going to pay six figures a month. I mean, that's just not realistic.
But some of these services are. And that's what makes them so incredible, right? Companies like 24 seven, you just get enough billing volume there. Like the numbers are the numbers.
So it's not a hyperbole or a hype, but we want to… as the business gets out there and gets competitive, you know, starts to really get out there with EHP, um… And Cole's going to talk about, you know, where that gets dialed in today. Ehp is going to do, you know, I've gone to, you know, I've got a really tight, in fact, Marty's down here at my house this Saturday. I'm taking the Everglades fishing. I'm not going to feed them to crocodiles because he's too important. So we're gonna let him catch some tarp and have a great time.
But I've also, my course regions really taking care of you all, right? He knows you're professional consultants for a living. That's what we do, or the… we're a very unique company in the whole entire marketplace of the US.
And so, because of that, you're going to get rewarded for that. So we're going to do 2 things. We're going to go back in, and we're going to get you more money up front on EHP deals. And I don't know what that is yet.
But it's gonna happen soon. Don't hold off on deals, because starting today on, if you submit something, I'll make sure that's honored from today on. So you don't delay in submitting a client. But you're going to get more dollars on your HP business. And I think that's going to be incredible, but also.
Because I'm trying to educate you all the path, it's not who you know, it's who else knows other people that you don't know. Leveraging is the path to wealth. Residuals is one thing, but when you can bring leveraging on other people's relationships that are outside your own, that's acceleration.
to wealth. And so you can sit there and just recruit people and get wealthy. And we're about to make that easier because you're going to get paid more money on the people you go recruit for EHP, okay? And it's going to be outside of their standard offering, outside of what they do.
Okay, so… so that's going to be pretty cool. So we're going to make that announcement soon, and we'll still have a bonus structure in there, but it's going to be an epic situation for you, so it really sets you up. So that's one small company will still pay you a fortune. So you don't need a lot of volume with this to do really well. That's a great thing we like about EHP.
It's like people in the beginning go like, Oh, I know a $50,000 company. Not going to happen. So so we really got this dialed in now, and I want to thank Cole for the extra help that he does. I want to thank Tammy Kucher, because we built our own. Of course, Leslie and Betsy and our entire staff, Timmy.
We've added another whole layer of support because it's necessary to help you win inside of EHP. So I want to thank the staff, the team that makes that plausible. And I'm telling you, it's not always clean. But there's that's just how business works, folks.
Business ain't clean, right? It's just, it's not a perfect world. I mean, that's that that used to be called Disneyland, right? And when we were young, right? We thought that was the perfect world until we wised up. So so anyways, that there is no so perfect world. So so, you know, know what's going to fit in the box.
And Cole's going to talk about that today a little bit, like, what the ideal clients are, what they're looking for. They're either gonna love it, or they're not gonna… they're not gonna handle it. There's a couple things that we can do.
tell them to get over the box, but… but Cole will talk about that, and I'm going to encourage you to also learn from his pitch today of what's working and resonating with companies, right? Because if you get too detailed about it, now you're doing the discovery person's job. And by the way, they've added more people in the discovery call desk, they've got a lot more employees. I mean, it's.
It's starting to rise up, right? But it still takes time, which is why we put other services in front of you, so that while you're waiting on that EHP business, don't put your eggs in one basket, everybody. You should have multiple. So you own a cost savings consulting company, right? If that client benefits.
I guarantee they're going to benefit from auto stock, just as they're going to benefit from EHP. If they're in the medical field, they're going to definitely benefit from 24-7 instantly, and you're going to get big fast. They're going to benefit from Legacy One going out there and offering, you know, legal shields, you know, on the business solution side of that, bringing that as voluntary benefits up front. These are the types of things that move the needle.
with your clients that bring great value with a great team. And so we got some new services coming out, and we've got some which is actually 4 in 1, and we've got some, uh, some things that are really rising to the top, like, 24-7. So I want to congratulate everyone, but no matter what, I think.
Cole, everyone has always stayed very interested in EHP no matter what. Like, it's just a fascinating service. It's different. It is, you know, an explanation to it, but you are going to get a little bit more dollars in the pocket here. So I, you know, pre-congratulations to all of you. It's coming, it's coming up. So, um… I'm excited about that. But Cole, we have some new folks on here, so why don't we talk through? I'm going to hand this call over to you, my friend, and I want to introduce Cole Nevin. He's out of Arkansas. Great, incredible guy. He's on the proposal. He's done everything. He's done discovery calls, but he's now he's doing proposal calls. So he's like he's closing up for clients for you.
Okay.
He's one of those guys at DHP, and he's really a great individual. We love his leadership, and so, Cole, we appreciate you, brother. So I'm going to hand this over to you and let you take it away. And then we're going to kind of come back and talk about the bonus again that we have. I want to remind you guys about it, but we're going to make recruiting.
inside a bigger deal for you, so you're really going to want to start sharing the news with people, because you're going to make a fortune.
off of getting other people involved in EHP, right? So we're going to do that. So, Cole, take it away, brother.
Nice. Yes, absolutely. Thank you very much, Sean. I, yeah, and I'm excited to hear a little bit more. And I know there's not going to be all the details now on the, um.
Some adjustments there, but it's definitely exciting as far as pay and everything else. So, that's awesome. You know, one thing I was thinking, you had mentioned ideal clients, and I thought maybe I'd start with that. I'm going to go through.
Kind of a condensed… so a lot of times on the proposal calls.
Somebody will get to that call, and they were not on the discovery call, they weren't on any of the previous calls, and then they're just coming in to hear the numbers, and so they don't really know about the program. So a lot of times I'll do, like, a short discovery call right there, then we'll go into their proposal.
And then kind of go from there. So… so that's what I was thinking, is we're gonna just do a short discovery call, but before I even do that, I wanted to also mention… Couple things that you had talked about, Sean, the ideal clients, and then also…
the process, because I think if you have a big picture, it can really help with.
what to expect, because, you know, when you're expecting one thing, and then you get something else, and it's like, it's, you know, it's that whole… it can get frustrating, but if you kind of have an idea, like, okay, it's going to go here, this is gonna take a week or two, or whatever, and then it's going to go here, and so if you kind of see that. So anyway, so I wanted to just mention that.
It's the first thing is, of course, the discovery call. And actually, what I'm going to do is, as we go through this, these slides, there's that one slide that you I'm sure many of you are very familiar with where it where it shows the discovery shows the census and then the proposal. And I'm just going to spend a little bit more detail on that than I normally would just to kind of.
Go through that with everybody, because I think that'll help. So… Without anything else, I'm going to go ahead and share my screen, and I'm going to roll through like a condensed discovery call for especially for those that are new. And and if you're… and if you've seen this quite a few times, I'm going to make it a little bit, you know, again, a little bit condensed, so don't.
Don't worry about it, um, and we're going to cover some really neat things, I think, after this as well, and hopefully maybe get a few questions answered and stuff as well.
So let me go ahead and share my screen.
and we will jump in here. So one of the first things, too, is this this first slide is preventive care program. This is really if I have 25 seconds with somebody, this is kind of like my my 25 second pitch is this 1st slide is this? This is a preventive care management program that's all about adding some practical benefits for the employees.
At zero out-of-pocket cost the employee, and then not only is it zero out of pocket to the employer, but you're going to save in, like, four different ways, including thousands of dollars on FICA taxes.
All of this is without replacing anything. It's just… it sits on top of your regular health, and it complements it, it enhances it, it's just an incredible benefit for the employees and a total win for the employer. So that's… That's the, uh… that's really my… my elevator pitch if I had to have one. It's kind of that first slide right there.
One thing I always mention is that healthcare is a disaster. It's expensive. It's it's just not in a good situation right now. Um… And the government knows that. And I was at a at a meeting a while back, and I know I've mentioned this before, and many of you heard a lot of this stuff that I'll say. But anyway, I was at a meeting a while back, and there was a congressman there, and he said, it's not just that healthcare is expensive, and it's challenging, all this stuff right now, but he said there's no end in sight, and the projections are even worse than what it is now. So.
It's like, the government knows there's a real problem here. It's somewhat of a crisis, in fact, and they have for years, and they've been dealing with this. But in 2013, they made at least a push towards, like, the participatory model, the wellness program prevention, proactive wellness, that kind of thing. So.
They made that push. The problem was that very few people participated, that was one thing, and then the other thing was that there was just not real clarity on structure.
So in 2000. 21, there was an article in the Cpa Journal that basically spells out titles 20 questions about health and wellness in the workplace. And the author is a CPA, he's a tax attorney, he's a professor of law and taxation. And basically, he spells out a self-insured medical expense reimbursement program.
Which is the simmer, and then he also talks about the whimper, which is the wellness integrated medical plan expense reimbursement. The CIMRP actually, I believe, sits inside the WIMPR. The WIMPR is kind of the bigger, broader program. So… so we use those programs, and that's what we follow to a T, and that's what keeps us just fully in line and compliant with HIPAA and ERISA, with the IRS, and of course with the with the Aca as well.
So that's… that's… to me, that's a big point, that we just stick with the guidance that was the recommendation from the CPA Journal.
article, which is… which is awesome. That's… to me, that's very, very significant.
On the compliance side, I really don't get into much detail, but I just like to mention it's an integrated 105 plan, which just confirms that it has to be paired with a medical plan, so we're never looking to replace somebody's healthcare. This is actually an integrated 105. They have to have it.
There has to be paired with a with a health plan. So so that's one thing. The other thing is that 213D talks about what is compliantly reimbursable.
If they're 213D benefits, then then it's it's true medical care. So I'll talk a little bit about that in a minute, but.
kind of along those lines, because really the reimbursement is the whole key. It's the the wellness integrated medical expense reimbursement and the self-insured medical expense reimburse. That reimbursement is the key to the whole program. That's what makes it all work. That's what makes it so valuable for the employees.
And also for the employer. So this is as an example of one of the one of the things that, you know, EHP looks at as far as guidance. This is from the Irs publication 15, the employer's tax guide from last year on page 19. It just says very plainly regarding these reimbursements, it says.
Medical care reimbursements paid for an employee under an employer's self-insured medical reimbursement plan aren't wages, aren't subject to Social Security, Medicare, or fee taxes, or federal income tax withholding. So it is a non-taxable reimbursement that comes after taxes, which is awesome. And again, that's what makes the whole thing.
So beneficial. So… Regarding eligibility, this is something that I know a couple months ago there was a kind of an announcement, and Ehp had had announced that, hey, it's no longer 20 or more employees. Now we're going to go down to 10, and we could even go down to 5, and some of you may have heard that even go down to 5. But the problem.
And we're kind of, like, shifting, at least from what it seems and what I've heard, is that we're kind of shifting to back to the 20 range, just because there's some fantastic companies that would be a great fit with 12, 15 employees. But a lot of times what happens is the companies will come in.
They might have 12 employees, 15 employees. But then, as we start to go through that process, and they put their senses together, and then we get to the proposal card, and we find out there's like 6 that qualify. And then now we're down to where.
It's like, and it's… and a lot of it has to do with industry, and that's the thing I wanted to just talk for a second about was.
the ideal client. So if somebody has, you know, 13, 15 employees, it can work if they're all full time, decent wages.
And, you know, then that could be a really good situation. If it's… if it's low income, it's going to be tougher, and it's a bummer, but it is one of those things that… If somebody is single with 0 dependence, no deductions, they might make 223,000 and still qualify. But if somebody is is married, and then they have a couple kids, and then they have a $700 health deduction.
Even if they make $45,000, it's like, with all those deductions and credits and stuff, then they're taxable wages are going to be down, you know, less than the single person that makes 23, 24,000. So they and then they won't qualify. They might make 40,000 and not qualify or 45 or even more sometimes if depending on the children and dependents and.
And and also what they're putting away in 401k and other pre-tax deductions. So… so it's a lot that goes into that. But I guess what I'm saying is that the ideal client is going to have decent wages, consistent income.
and and really, ideally, it's going to be 20 or more employees. It's not going to be, you know, much less than that, unless if it's an accounting firm, or if it's, like, which we've done, it's always… I'm always intrigued, and I love it when we… when we onboard accounting firms, because there's, you know, maybe there's only 15 employees, but these are all CPAs, and we had a couple of those go through the other day, actually, a law firm, an accounting firm.
Um, similar, uh, joint ownership. But anyway, that's always awesome. That always, to me, speaks, you know, speaks a lot about the credibility and the, um, the compliance and all that stuff. So anyway… But yeah, but 20 or more is ideal for sure. So when you're talking to businesses, just keep that in mind. Somebody said the other day it was actually Will who does a lot of the discovery calls. He says, I would much rather lose a deal on the front end than on the back end. So, in other words.
Let's just try to weed it out up front. If it's not a good fit, then let's not waste everybody's time getting the census and going through and, you know, back and forth. And then we get down to the to the to the proposal call, and it's like, or even… even farther sometimes, but… and to where.
It's just it doesn't really make sense, and I've had a few lately that I've sent on to onboarding, but I have to warn them, I say, hey, I don't even know if this is gonna go. I don't know if EHP is gonna allow this, because there's, you know, out of the 19, there's only 9 that qualify, and then… and some of them need a.
And so it's just, it gets really complicated. So just keep that stuff in mind as you're as you're prospecting, as you're talking to businesses. If it's… if it's low, just, you know, be kind of forewarned that there is a chance that that deal may just end up.
not working for EHP. So that's that. The other thing is.
I probably spent way too long there, but anyway, I'm going to go through really quick on the benefits. So, everybody knows Revive, but Revive is awesome. It's an incredible platform, and that's why there's 4.8 million employees that use it. Um, we just used it a couple weeks ago. My son, in the middle of the night, we're trying to go to bed, and my youngest, who's 13, he… He… he throws up, and then he… he turns white, and he steps out, and then he just passes out, and I'm like, oh my gosh, my wife's kind of, you know, worried, obviously, and so I go in, I put the request in on Revive, and then, um, it was… it was the middle of the night, so usually it's, like, 3 to 5 minutes is typically what people will get, like, you know, a response back with the doctor, but.
This was in the middle of the night, so it was like 10 to 15 minutes, but we got a doctor on the phone.
She's got at least 10 years clinical experience. She's U.S. Board certified. This was a lady. There's obviously men and women that are these physicians, but… They're all exclusive to revive, which is awesome, so they're not working for us health centers and whoever else they might, you know, some of those doctors right out of college might just be doing different programs. So these are exclusive. They're 10 years experience. So it's just awesome that in the middle of the night.
You can get a doctor on the phone that has experience that can give you true advice. It's amazing. So there's 5 main areas here. There's the urgent care, the primary care, the medications, the weight health, and the mental health.
None of it's meant to replace their primary doctor. None of it's meant to replace their health insurance. It's just another resource. The urgent care is an awesome resource. The primary care can be. I'm gonna just roll through this quick. The medications. There's a thousand medications. Revive owns the formulary, so there's 1,000 that are just free. That's… That's been one of the biggest things, and even for groups that have really good insurance, this is one thing that that they're still very interested in because even if they have great insurance and all this other coverage, they still have copays, they still have costs.
And they're still spending a lot of money on medication, so if they can add something like this, where even if they have a telemedicine, even if they have some of the other things, there's a little duplication there, that's fine. They can still save a fortune just by the medications.
Um, through Revive. And then of course they'll use some of the other stuff anyway. The mental health is awesome. There's a hundred group sessions per week. There's of course the one-on-one sessions with a master's level clinician. And then there's the weight health.
And this whole thing is like a membership. It's like you… once an employee enrolls, they get unlimited access to everything with… with one exception, and it's all free, it's all included for their spouse, up to 5 dependents, but the weight medication is the one thing that is… that is additional. It's just enormously reduced pricing.
So. One of the neat things about Revive is that it's one company that provides all these different components. So it is… It's just… it makes for a much more streamlined process for the employees experience than other programs where they might be pieced together with a telemedicine vendor and a fitness vendor and a mental health vendor and all these different companies that you're dealing with. This is just a little bit.
I would say a lot, actually, more streamlined experience for employees.
So, one of my favorite things to talk about, too, is this little part right here. So there's the reporting that's available for employees. I'm sorry, for employers to be able to see and track utilization and savings and stuff like that, but.
A lot of this is for businesses that are self-insured.
I know we've talked about this, but if you're new, this is significant. And Scott, last week on a call, Scott Moeller, he's got the insurance background. Scott's awesome. He has great insights on things. But anyway, he just confirmed on a call.
that some of you may have been on, that if it's… if it's self-insured, if it's self-funded, if it's level funded, all these different terms, if they're captive, all these different terms that sometimes somebody will say, and it's like, I don't have an insurance background, I am licensed, but I don't have that background.
Sometimes I'll get kind of thrown off by some of that stuff, but he just confirmed that that's all basically in the same bucket, and it's either that or they're fully insured, or… Or sometimes they might say fully funded. But basically, that's that's pretty much it. So most of those other terms are going to be, and really the groups that that will benefit the most from this. Everybody's going to benefit. If somebody's fully insured, they're going to still get great savings on… in all these areas, including the health.
Because it'll minimize claims, but when they're self-insured, it's more dollar for dollar. So then, like, EHP or actually Revive has done some studies, and they show some analytics that, like, every time an employee uses one of those components within Revive, specifically, like, the urgent care component.
It just saved that company $367 on average across the board, which is amazing. So it's a little more dollar for dollar when they're self-insured, but even when they're fully insured, it's going to minimize claims and help with that. And all of that happens because of this right here, this venue redirection.
It's intercepting all of those low-level claims, all of those unnecessary emergency room visits and everything else. So.
The big picture to me is what makes like the most sense. I was I was on a call a couple hours ago, and there was a lady.
She said she says, well, we don't. They didn't offer insurance. So that's that's one thing. But she said that most of her staff, because they don't have insurance, a lot of them were younger, and they just, uh… She said they go to the emergency room for everything because they don't have to pay for it. And I was like, oh my gosh, that's… now things are making even more sense to me, because I keep hearing, like, the average emergency room visit is, like, a $2,000 hit.
to this healthcare, you know, crisis over here. Every time somebody goes into urgent care, it's like a $500 hit to that healthcare situation.
So if people can use something like this, like, and when the lady that I was talking to, if her staff could tap into something like this, it's going to save the government millions of dollars if more businesses would use these programs. And that's exactly why the simmer program exists. That's exactly why the WIMPR.
program and these 213D, all these different codes and stuff like that. That's why they exist, because they… they have a crisis going on in this prevention structure is like a real answer to the crisis. So, to me, that's huge. And again, it never made… it was never more clear to me how valuable this is.
Then when that lady said, oh yeah, they just go to the emergency room for everything. I'm like, you gotta be kidding me! Like, for them, it's a hassle. They're taking hours, they're waiting over there and, you know, around a bunch of people in the emergency room that I don't ever want to be if I can't help it.
Um, and that kind of situation, but it's anyway, it's this financial thing. So.
This is a way they can… they can get access to doctors immediately, you know, within minutes, they can get medical care and advice and all of that, and then get prescriptions and everything else, um, you know, right from their house, right from wherever they are, and it doesn't hit the health insurance crisis over there, which.
Yeah, again, in the big picture, that's what makes so much sense. So… I am probably way over my, uh, short overview, but I've added a few other things that I don't normally maybe throw in on a regular, uh, condensed discovery, but…
I'll just go through this really quick. And then and then we'll wrap it up here in just a couple of minutes. But.
This is the sample paycheck. A lot of you are very familiar with this. If you're new, I'm going to go through it really fast. So this is without our program. This is with our program. So this employee makes $44,000 a year, 3,705 monthly.
Is there gross pay? Their health contribution is 465. If they had any other 125 deduction, it'd be right here. In this case they don't, so they're taxable income is 3,240. Then they have their federal state, social Medicare total taxes are 822, and then their take home.
This is now with our plan, so it's $3705, same gross, same contribution to health, we add the wellness program, it's a 1220 deduction.
And right now, going down, this is just a standard $125 deduction. Later, you'll see that it's going to be reimbursed down here within this SEMR program.
So it's a it's a line item, essentially, that's going to be a wash, but right now, it's a standard $125 deduction that reduces their taxable income down to 2020 in this example, and then respectively reducing each of those taxes. So instead of 822, now that employee only owes $513 in taxes.
So they just saved $309 that last month they were sending straight to taxes. Now they have that available to use on prevention and whatever else they want. And so what has to happen, though, is that 149.
fee comes out of that savings to cover the PCM, which is just as preventive care management program.
And then what's left over, in this case is 160, remains in their paycheck and increases their take-home pay.
So everybody gets a raise in a sense. And the reason that it's increasing their take home pay is because of that reimbursement. That's the beauty of the whole program. So the reason that the reimbursement is allowed, though, is because what's provided here.
is true 213D compliant medical care that the employee, their spouse, and up to five dependents have 24-7 access to all year long. So that's that's why the reimbursement fits. That's why it's allowed within the SEMR program.
is because it's actual medical care that everybody has access to. And so… That's kind of how it works on the employee. For the employer, they no longer excuse me, they no longer owe the FICA tax match on that 1220. So they save a gross amount of 9333 per month.
We have a $40 admin fee on the back end. It's always going to be the employer is always going to be positive with this program. They're never going to have to come out of pocket for anything initially. It's only going to be pay after you save. You save this amount, and at the end of the month you pay a little portion of that back to EHP.
And that's how it is with here. They save 93 in the month. They pay 40 at the end of the month. They're left with $53 net savings. So it's like a total win for the employer, and it's a total win for the employee.
on the financial side. So I'm going to skip this proposal. I love the proposals. This is really my favorite stage, and I'm so I'm I really enjoy doing those proposal calls.
And I wanted to say, too, on that, with the proposals, there's a lot of businesses that don't ask all of those tough questions, like about the 1220, or this or that, or whatever it is. There are a lot, obviously, that do, and I'm sure many of you have experienced those questions, and you're.
you know, reaching out to whoever to try to get some solid answers to some of those things, but wish there are. I usually get them from Scott Moeller, but I don't want to… I don't want you to blow up his phones. But anyway, Scott's awesome. He has, uh, yeah, he's awesome. But anyway.
But there's a lot of businesses that go right through. They come to their proposal, they see their numbers, we're saving $74,000, all these employees are saving this, we take the fee, they've taken home this.
and they're ready to go. It's like, they may ask a few little miscellaneous questions, like, okay, now, how are we going to get this invoice, and how do we pay that, or whatever? But it's like, they just go forward into onboarding, and then they go active on April 1st, or March 1st, or whenever it was, and so… I just want to encourage you guys with that, because some businesses get skeptical. They start asking these questions. They talk to their broker, they do whatever, and they get, you know, cold feet or whatever.
But a lot don't. So just keep talking to more, and you'll find some that's like they don't really care about those questions. They just want to save some money and provide some additional benefits, and they're in, and they're ready to go, and they go active, and it's just a smooth process.
There are a lot of businesses out there that, if they know about it, they're going to go for it, and it's going to be a win for everybody. So so I wanted to just to mention that.
This is what I wanted just to spend a moment on, and then I'll kind of close out here.
Of course, you want to get them to a discovery call. That's the 1st thing. From there, you want to stay involved and remember, you're the glue. You're the only constant in this whole process for those groups that you bring in. They're in fact, they are your client.
and they're really not EHP's client until they actually sign the Msa. Then they become EHC's client, and then there. But they're still your client. So as the affiliates, it's like we're… As an affiliate professionals, and these are our clients that are, you know, that you're bringing into EHP or.
whatever. And so you want to stay involved, you want to know what's going on. Sometimes I know it's kind of difficult, because maybe they do a call, or they didn't invite you to the call, and there's certain things, because of privacy and whatever, and if the client… maybe they… maybe you have a great relationship with them.
Um, maybe you don't. So either way, you want to stay as close as you can, but but sometimes, you know, depending on those things, you… you may not be, uh, you know, they may not add you as a guest on the… on the invite for the proposal call, or for the onboarding call, or whatever. But, um, but I just wanted to basically just give you kind of the nutshell. So there's a discovery.
help them get that census. It shouldn't take long, but sometimes it takes months. It just depends. It's only because they're dragging their feet, or they don't know what to do, and they need help, but… so anyway, it really should be done in about 20 to 30 minutes. Once that's done, we go to that proposal call.
Most of the time, yesterday, I think it was 3 out of 4 went straight into onboarding.
Most of the time they go, they move to onboarding after that proposal call.
Yeah, I think it was 3 out of 4 yesterday. I was thinking maybe it was 4 out of 5, but the other thing was only 4 yesterday of the proposal cost. So anyway, um, they moved forward, and then… and then from there, the next stop for them is an onboarding call. The onboarding call is usually with Asian or Stephanie.
And they're gonna essentially lay out those next steps for them, which is this which is really the group webinar. After that onboarding call is when they actually get their MSA, and they get their intake form, which will get the rest of the information for those employees. But then they go from that onboarding call.
They're going to be planning a group webinar for all their staff.
And then after that, they are going to be launching their enrollment, and that's where that's the enrollment launch, and then whether it's an assisted enroll or an auto enroll, however it is, there's going to be a window of period for that open enrollment, and then after that. And so also they're going to do at that same time, they're going to take a look at a previous payroll run before their open enrollment, and then they're going to always run a mock payroll.
after enrollment, so that they can make sure everything's integrated correctly, all the codes are entered correctly, and it's all good to go live on the 1st of that following month.
So sometimes they'll even do the mock payroll at the first of the month, that first payroll of the month, and they'll use that one as the mock. They'll test it, make sure, and then it's… and then it's live after that. So that first few days of the month is not always… it's not always just active on the first. Sometimes it's like the third or the fourth, depending on when they do that run, if they couldn't do it before that.
that mock payroll. So, and then it's live. And then from there we have a post-enrollment team that… Normally does a fantastic job. You're always, nobody's perfect and there's always going to be some times where somebody reaches out and they didn't get something, or something got lost or whatever, but normally it's a really solid post-enrollment team that does a really good job with, uh, you know, with getting questions answered for employees and employers and stuff, so…
Sean, is there anything you want me to zero in on? Because I got really one more thing that I'll just mention real quick, and then and then let me know if you wanted to zero in on anything, or if there's any questions. I haven't looked or anything, but let me know.
No, just… just hit the script again really hard, and then we're gonna pull up the bonus here at the end.
Okay, okay, awesome, awesome. So, alrighty, just, I guess, just really quick here is one of the things that's really important to people is is how much work is this going to be? And I always tell people it's not going to be a ton of work. We do 90 plus percent of the heavy lifting. We need somebody on your side to quarterback it.
coordinate things. And one of the clients that I had worked with really close, and I worked close with the CFO, they started last June 1st. They had about 180 employees, and he said just recently, he said.
We have, um, we've had one person, through the whole onboarding process that was the only contact with EHP.
She handles, like, HR and payroll, so she was, like, the main contact. Um, the only contact. And she did everything, and he said it was streamlined, it was seamless, there weren't any issues, and so… and that's still with her doing all of her regular duties. So, I tell people that lately, ever since he told me that a couple weeks ago, because.
It just lets people know, if they've got, you know, 50 employees or 200 employees, or whatever, it's going to be a pretty we're going to do the heavy lifting. It's not like you got to hire three people to help get this thing going. We handle it for you. We just need some.
some coordination and quite cooperation with your side. So, that's one thing. We do the heavy lifting. The last thing is, you know, all these insurance companies have vetted and approved EHP.
Allstate, Manhattan Life, Transamerica specifically have some of their in-house benefit brokers refer back to EHP to run this. They write some supplemental benefits, so it's just a… it's an… to me, that speaks volumes of compliance, and then also of just the structure.
processes and that that we have in place to get.
businesses through an active, um, or else, you know, Manhattan and Allstate and Transamerica would not be would not be be working with EHP the way they do, um, if that wasn't the case. So anyway, that to me as well. So that's the nutshell right there. Um, I'm gonna stop sharing, and I guess the last thing on that script is just that.
You know, healthcare is expensive. I've never heard more conversations about it as I have in the last 4 months, and I've heard many people. I say the average is probably 15 to 20 something percent increases, but a lot of them are 30 something. I've heard a few that are like 42% increase, which I don't even know how.
That's possible. But it's like it's really a problem. And I think it's something that almost everybody relates to, and I think it's a great way to kind of start those conversations or get them.
uh, get them to the table is by helping with that.
Great. Awesome. Cole, great job as always. We're gonna hit Q&A here in a second. Leslie, can you pull up the bonus?
I want to remind everyone that even though you're going to receive.
This is in place right now. But this is where, you know, depending on where you're at.
Can… can really level this up and scale it up dramatically, because all this is added on top of each other, right? So if you.
do the math. That's another $12 added on top of this and peplum increase, right? So we're probably gonna, you're going to this may be adjusted when we bring a new thing, but you're your starting date is going to be bigger. Hello. Your starting gate is going to be bigger.
You're welcome. So I was… Do a little bit of this, and working on that. So… so we'll let you know what that is. But right now, as of today, submit your discovery calls in. We'll make it retroactive as of today, just because I announced it. I wanted to let you guys know there's more coming there, and on recruiting.
Because I want to tell you that it's not just who you know, it's who other people know, and you'll make… there's some people already cashing in. Now, look, we have probably 30,000 lives, um, intertwined right now that we're in the.
Well, we've already got multiple tons of closed deals, but we have 30,000 plus employees tracking through our system right now that's in onboarding. And so we're in stages like that. So… you know, it took a while to build it, but it's there now. So, like Cole said, it just takes one, and now it's like chopping wood. But it's… and some of you have had to put up some business and get through it, but that's… that's business, right? It's… no one said it'd be easier. I mean, I know that it might handle more than, but in the beginning, you gotta find people that are.
you know, it's a new program, right? You're educating most of America on this, and and and I'll address it this way. So we could take that down. Thanks, Leslie. So, Stan, you know, per your question.
I don't… I'm not gonna sit here and address other companies. I really care less what other companies do, to be honest. Like, you know, I chose them because this this tax system is a full… it's at least 4 plus tax codes. It's just this is not created out of thin air. Stan. This is a similar program. It's been around for a long time. People just have no idea it works in 4 tax codes. It's very straightforward.
In fact, if you just watch Cole's presentation, I think it speaks for itself. So that shows the tax benefits and then revive shows the what? The health benefits, the wellness benefits to their employees, right? They have five benefits, and that's that's where I like to focus more on, because I think that's what's more important these days.
Um, and helping bring some relief to the massive healthcare increases that Cole has talked about, that everyone's experienced, which is dramatically cool, in my opinion, since January. I mean, it's been… the whole thing has shifted, and it's been crazy like people don't have a choice. There's nowhere for American companies to go to right now for relief. What are they going to do?
Yeah.
Think about it. They're self-insured. What's their options? And and someone's gonna, you know, someone's gonna some of them are passing on to their employees. Some of them are eating it themselves.
And that just means it's lesser second highest expense on their P&L, right? Outside of payroll. So think about that for a second, right? Let that marinate for a little bit. So it's not rocket science, it's just are they comfortable or not? One thing I've learned about EHP and just the service in general, but pioneering new things for 25 years.
I was the first guy bringing virtual cards in the United States. Very first guy. Cfos had no clue what a virtual card was. Now every bank offers it. Every person offers it. It's out there. We're taking people away from banks with my $4 billion fintech company.
We still had CFOs questioning what a virtual card was and if it was legitimate. No difference here. Not many people know about it. They're either going to love it.
Or they're going to get weary of it, and you're not going to convince them either way of it. Right, Cole? I mean, there's… we have the E&O, there's some angles that we can take.
No.
But you want to have your client comfortable with it. They need to be comfortable with what is going on there. And there's protections on it. But anyways, we have found those 20.
to under 1,000 move. very efficiently through the process. And and so I've really gotten people out of the clouds and gotten into reality. I like to live in reality, because that's how I get business done. And and those are people that are actually going to close business.
So, um, but I wanted to kind of, you know, throw that out there, so hopefully Stan… and Joe said he had a killer, um, 200 employees, so if it passed the limits test, he'll recommend it to nine other companies owned by his friends. That's awesome. I mean, it's… You're gonna get a lot of those one-to-many. Dave wanted to know if you can reiterate EHP can benefit hospital medical practice.
Yeah, so that's a good question. It's a little different approach. I would say, when you're talking to a group like an insurance company or like a medical clinic or a hospital, because they have their in-house clinics. They have all their stuff. So it is a little different. There was one hospital I was talking to, and he said, well.
I mean, we give away our medications for free as well, like, to some of our staff, like, they can get all these, you know, a lot of basic medications at no cost, but we're still paying for them, and I was like, okay, yeah, so he said, so we're, you know, it's still a win for us, because if Revive's paying for them, that's better for us anyway.
Anyway, um, it's a little different approach. I would say with a medical hospital clinics and stuff like that, I think it's probably better to take the payroll tax savings approach.
Because they have a lot of benefits, they have all this other stuff. They have all their telemedicines, they have everything kind of situated. So this is still going to save them money on that side, on the health side. But I think what is, especially if it's a larger group, what's probably going to be more.
impactful, and is that payroll tax savings that they're going to be able to get by implementing the preventive care program.
Lee wants to know if EHP offers auto protection as well.
Yes. Yeah, they're they've just made those changes to that. But it's it's even. So we've never had to use it. But for years there's always been some kind of a legal expense insurance or or fund like that. But.
It doesn't have to be… It used to be where you'd have to use one of EHP's attorneys. Now that they have it set where they can choose an attorney and go… and it's going to be covered within that plan. But the bigger thing there is that E&O policy. They have the new $20 million E&O policy, which is basically acts as an indemnification for the client, so if EHP made an error, the IRS said, hey, they didn't do this right.
It's not compliant, whatever. There's a $20 million policy that's every every client is covered under, and that's really the bigger probably answer to that.
and one wants to know, he says he has 175-person company that has a little bit of cold feet. They said, like, too good to be true, right? So what could you recommend? Send them the simmer Cpa case study question mark?
Do you have any recommendations?
I'm not sure what the SEMRP CPA case study is, but I would say, you know what? We just, I heard this lady that she runs this business and they don't have health insurance and all of her staff is running to the emergency room every time.
Of course, the government wants this program. Like, the government's drowning because of these kind of situations. Like, of course they want this program. It makes so much sense in the big picture. That's what I would tell her, is I would tell her the big picture, or tell them the big picture. I'd say.
Healthcare is a crisis. It's extremely expensive. The government spends, like, 30-something percent of that $5 trillion.
And if we can't prevent some of this stuff, it's going to continue to get even worse.
And I like the questions, like, so what do you, you know, what's your deductibles? And how about your employees? What's your plan? Asking the client, you know, what's your plan? How are you planning to to handle that? Because if you start there, they don't have a plan.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
you know, you do have a plan, right? Peter is 20 million. And so that's that's how that works. But Joe and and and I want to congratulate all those people that, you know, have got business clothes. That's great. Congratulations. We're gonna make. It's even gonna be, you know, this is a great year for this, because everyone's feeling the pinch.
Yep.
The economy in general is feeling the pinch. So, um, but with the healthcare increases, it's just prime now, you guys. So, and I think you're getting sharp on your presentations, and because of that, and because of the volume that we've done as a company, you all are going to get more money. So congratulations. That's.
Nice.
That's because all of you jointly working together have made an impression, you know, with EHP. So congratulations. Right. And in putting that forward. So Nicole, I appreciate your leadership too in this. You've been a superstar, buddy. And Tammy, I know you're out there and everyone else that's, you know, participating working with this. It's been great.
So, look, keep your presentation simple. Do not get in the weeds on this program. You're going to lose your deal. That is the deal. I mean, you start trying to explain this. You just might. You just you just kissed all that time goodbye. You just wasted it, because it's not going to happen. Get them to a discovery call. They even have more people down the discovery call desk.
That they've trained. These guys… these people are really doing a good job. And then Wednesdays, EHP themselves do a deep dive, usually Mike Culver is doing that call on Wednesdays at 3 Eastern, and carving that down. We're going to do some different stuff on ops, because we've already created our own landing pages for for recruiting.
over the EHP stuff, so we've got our own stuff for recruiting, and now it's about to get really sick, because you're going to get more money on your recruits, right? So it's gonna be pretty fun. So we're excited for you. So so get ready, like, because it's who do you know right? So now you know it's going to be who else? Somebody else.
knows, right? Because they're going to have a relationship that you don't, and that's going to really pay some big dividends for you here shortly. So I love it. Cole, anything in closing?
No.
Nope, I just say stay positive. It's it's not easy, but it's worth it, because businesses are rolling through and just kind of be consistent, and if one's got cold feet, just go on to another one. Keep in contact with them. Don't try to convince them. Just just keep getting more to that pipeline, and there's going to be some of those that are going to be dropping in.
Yep. Right? Right.
Yeah. Yep.
Stay with it, right? If you put up a couple, you're not going to be successful, because the law of averages aren't going to be in your favor, right? This is a you got to put up consistent business to get some through. But when you get them through, it's worth it, because you get paid really well for not a lot of employees.
Yep. Yeah.
Thank you, Sean.
Right? And you're about to get, you know, even more. So it's it's really great and worth it. So thank you, Cole, for your leadership, brother. I appreciate you, as always. And good job. And everybody, we'll see you on the AI call tomorrow. Be ready for 24 7 next week. That's going to be awesome for the, uh, for the, uh.
Yep.
AR deal, that's… that's a hot potato, and just be consistent, right? We appreciate you guys. We'll see everyone on that training that we have on the 18th for level one and two with Legacy One, all that stuff. Any way we can support, make sure you send us an email, let us know, but stay plugged into your calls.
Your